<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Charlotte Gonzalez, Author at CoV Media</title>
	<atom:link href="https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/author/charlottegonzalez/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/author/charlottegonzalez/</link>
	<description>Where Gaming Dreams Come to Life!</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 20:15:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>How to Fix DLL Errors in Games</title>
		<link>https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/how-to-fix-dll-errors-in-games/</link>
					<comments>https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/how-to-fix-dll-errors-in-games/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charlotte Gonzalez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 20:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Banners]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/?p=1178</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Are you frustrated by annoying DLL errors that disrupt your gaming experience? Don&#8217;t worry we&#8217;ve got you covered with this comprehensive guide on how to...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[</p>
<p><p>Are you frustrated by annoying DLL errors that disrupt your gaming experience? Don&#8217;t worry  we&#8217;ve got you covered with this comprehensive guide on how to fix DLL errors in games. DLL (Dynamic Link Library) errors can be a common issue, but with the right steps, you can get back to enjoying your favorite games without any interruptions. Let&#8217;s dive into the solutions!</p>
</p>
<div class="bf_toc_container">
<div class="bf_toc_title">Table Of Contents</div>
<nav>
<ol>
<li><a href="#bf_toc_1" title="Identifying the Source of the Error">Identifying the Source of the Error</a></li>
<li><a href="#bf_toc_2" title="Updating Drivers and Software">Updating Drivers and Software</a></li>
<li><a href="#bf_toc_3" title="Reinstalling or Repairing the Game">Reinstalling or Repairing the Game</a></li>
<li><a href="#bf_toc_4" title="Using System File Checker (SFC)">Using System File Checker (SFC)</a></li>
<li><a href="#bf_toc_5" title="Final Thoughts">Final Thoughts</a></li>
</ol>
</nav>
</div>
<h3 id="bf_toc_1">Identifying the Source of the Error</h3>
<p><img alt='gamehall-org-cardgames-dll-error-1751627' alt="how to fix dll errors in games" src='https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/gamehall.org-cardgames-dll-error-1751627.jpg'/></p>
<p>Before you start fixing DLL errors, it&#8217;s crucial to identify the source of the error. DLL errors can occur due to various reasons such as missing or corrupted files, outdated drivers, or even malware infections. Make sure to read the error message carefully to understand what might be causing the issue.</p>
<p>Additionally, you can use diagnostic tools and software to scan for potential issues and pinpoint the exact DLL file causing the error. This will give you a clearer direction on how to proceed with the fix.</p>
</p>
<p><h3 id="bf_toc_2">Updating Drivers and Software</h3>
<p><img alt='gamehall-org-minecraft-error-0xc00007b-featured-5535191' alt="how to fix dll errors in games" src='https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/gamehall.org-minecraft-error-0xc00007b-featured-5535191.jpg'/></p>
<p>Outdated drivers and software can often lead to DLL errors in games. To tackle this, ensure that your graphics card, audio drivers, and other essential components are up-to-date. Visit the official websites of your hardware manufacturers to download and install the latest driver updates.</p>
<p>Similarly, keep your operating system and the game itself updated to the latest version. Developers frequently release patches and updates to address compatibility issues and fix DLL-related errors.</p>
</p>
<p><h3 id="bf_toc_3">Reinstalling or Repairing the Game</h3>
<p><img alt='gamehall-org-binkw64-dll-4329715' alt="how to fix dll errors in games" src='https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/gamehall.org-binkw64-dll-4329715.jpg'/></p>
<p>If a specific game is giving you DLL errors, try reinstalling or repairing the game. Sometimes, the game&#8217;s installation files can become corrupted, causing DLL issues. To do this, go to your game library, right-click on the game, and select the option to reinstall or repair. This process will replace any missing or damaged DLL files related to the game.</p>
</p>
<p><h3 id="bf_toc_4">Using System File Checker (SFC)</h3>
<p><img alt='gamehall-org-phps85poo1g81-3526919' alt="how to fix dll errors in games" src='https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/gamehall.org-phps85poo1g81-3526919.jpg'/></p>
<p>Windows includes a handy tool called System File Checker (SFC) that can help fix corrupted system files, including DLLs. To use SFC, open the Command Prompt as an administrator and type the command &#8220;<code>sfc /scannow</code>&#8220;. The tool will scan your system and replace any corrupted or missing files with fresh copies from the Windows installation.</p>
<p>After the scan is complete, restart your computer and check if the DLL errors in your games have been resolved.</p>
</p>
<p><h3 id="bf_toc_5">Final Thoughts</h3>
<p><img alt='gamehall-org-steam-api-dll-6830041' alt="how to fix dll errors in games" src='https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/gamehall.org-steam-api.dll--6830041.jpg'/></p>
<p>Dealing with DLL errors in games can be frustrating, but with the right approach, you can overcome these issues and enjoy a seamless gaming experience. Remember to identify the source of the error, update drivers and software, reinstall or repair games, and use tools like the System File Checker to fix corrupted files.</p>
<p>If the problem persists after trying these solutions, consider seeking help from online gaming communities or technical support forums. Gamers often share their experiences and solutions to similar problems, and you might find the solution you need.</p>
</p>
<p><p>Happy gaming!</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/how-to-fix-dll-errors-in-games/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>When Does a Football Game Proceed to Overtime?</title>
		<link>https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/when-does-a-football-game-proceed-to-overtime/</link>
					<comments>https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/when-does-a-football-game-proceed-to-overtime/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charlotte Gonzalez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 09:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Banners]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/?p=1121</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Football, a sport filled with intense moments and unpredictable twists, often leaves fans on the edge of their seats. But what happens when the regulation...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Football, a sport filled with intense moments and unpredictable twists, often leaves fans on the edge of their seats. But what happens when the regulation time isn&#8217;t enough to determine a winner? That&#8217;s where overtime comes into play, adding an extra layer of excitement to the game. Let&#8217;s delve into the world of football and explore when a football game proceeds to overtime.</p>
<div class="bf_toc_container">
<div class="bf_toc_title">Table Of Contents</div>
<nav>
<ol>
<li><a href="#bf_toc_1" title="The Tension of Regulation Time">The Tension of Regulation Time</a></li>
<li><a href="#bf_toc_2" title="Overtime: A Shot at Redemption">Overtime: A Shot at Redemption</a></li>
<li><a href="#bf_toc_3" title="The Different Overtime Formats">The Different Overtime Formats</a></li>
<li><a href="#bf_toc_4" title="Embracing the Unpredictability">Embracing the Unpredictability</a></li>
</ol>
</nav>
</div>
<h3 id="bf_toc_1">The Tension of Regulation Time</h3>
<p><img alt='gamehall-org-texas-am-ot-win-090321-getty-ftr-1a0wn5s3nr6mu11bpu3aw3hz8d-7663285' alt="When does a football game proceed to overtime" src='https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/gamehall.org-texas-am-ot-win-090321-getty-ftr-1a0wn5s3nr6mu11bpu3aw3hz8d-7663285.jpg'/></p>
<p>As the clock ticks down during a football match, the tension builds. The teams battle it out on the field, strategizing and giving their all to secure victory within the regulation time. But what if, despite their efforts, the score remains tied when the referee signals the end of the second half? This is when the game takes an unexpected turn and heads into overtime.</p>
<h3 id="bf_toc_2">Overtime: A Shot at Redemption</h3>
<p><img alt='alabama-auburn-football' alt="When does a football game proceed to overtime" src='https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/gamehall.org-ceecpmsqpyi6za6s3hnlbyr3py-9745582.jpg'/></p>
<p>Entering overtime presents both teams with a fresh chance to break the tie and claim victory. The overtime format varies based on the level of play and the governing rules, but it generally involves additional periods of play, each lasting a specified duration. These periods can bring new strategies, renewed energy, and intensified gameplay as teams battle to outwit and outmaneuver their opponents.</p>
<h3 id="bf_toc_3">The Different Overtime Formats</h3>
<p><img alt='gamehall-org-nfl-overtime-092420-getty-ftrjpg-ujra23k7utg1rk4sxyu9re8i-8133040' alt="When does a football game proceed to overtime" src='https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/gamehall.org-nfl-overtime-092420-getty-ftrjpg-ujra23k7utg1rk4sxyu9re8i-8133040.jpg'/></p>
<p>Football has witnessed various overtime formats over the years, each designed to ensure fairness and excitement. One common format is the &#8220;golden goal&#8221; rule, where the first team to score during overtime wins the match instantly. Another format involves a predetermined number of extra minutes, typically two halves of 15 minutes each. If the tie persists after the additional time, the game might proceed to a penalty shootout, adding a dramatic conclusion to the battle.</p>
<h4>The Thrill of the Penalty Shootout</h4>
<p>Penalty shootouts are the ultimate nail-biting moments in football, determining the winner through a series of one-on-one battles between a designated player from each team and the opposing goalkeeper. These nerve-wracking moments often lead to unforgettable celebrations or heartbreaks. Players must summon their skills and composure to score while goalkeepers aim to make crucial saves that can alter the course of the match.</p>
<h3 id="bf_toc_4">Embracing the Unpredictability</h3>
<p><img alt='gamehall-org-4oyvvf22fzqqvxka5tfczii5qu-3840375' alt="When does a football game proceed to overtime" src='https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/gamehall.org-4oyvvf22fzqqvxka5tfczii5qu-3840375.jpg'/></p>
<p>Football is cherished for its unpredictability, and overtime adds an extra layer of uncertainty that captivates fans worldwide. The sudden shift in momentum, the chance for underdogs to rise, and the pressure-cooker situations in penalty shootouts all contribute to the beauty of the game. Overtime showcases the essence of football  the determination to triumph against all odds.</p>
<p>So, the next time you find yourself at the edge of your seat during a tied football match, remember that the excitement is far from over. Overtime brings a fresh wave of anticipation and drama, shaping the destiny of the game with every kick, pass, and save. Whether it&#8217;s the glorious goal in golden goal overtime or the nail-biting penalty shootout, football&#8217;s overtime moments are etched into the history of the sport, reminding us why we love the beautiful game.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/when-does-a-football-game-proceed-to-overtime/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Do One-Word Game Titles Work?</title>
		<link>https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/do-one-word-game-titles-work/</link>
					<comments>https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/do-one-word-game-titles-work/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charlotte Gonzalez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 16:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Backpacks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/?p=914</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[When it comes to naming a video game, the title is more than just a bunch of letters strung together it&#8217;s a glimpse into the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>When it comes to naming a video game, the title is more than just a bunch of letters strung together  it&#8217;s a glimpse into the world and experience that players can expect. While lengthy titles have their charm, there&#8217;s a growing trend in the gaming industry: one-word game titles. But do these succinct titles effectively convey the essence of a game and capture players&#8217; attention? Let&#8217;s delve into the intriguing realm of one-word game titles and explore whether they truly work.</p>
<div class="bf_toc_container">
<div class="bf_toc_title">Table Of Contents</div>
<nav>
<ol>
<li><a href="#bf_toc_1" title="The Allure of Simplicity">The Allure of Simplicity</a></li>
<li><a href="#bf_toc_2" title="The Intrigue of Mystery">The Intrigue of Mystery</a></li>
<li><a href="#bf_toc_3" title="Memorability and Impact">Memorability and Impact</a></li>
<li><a href="#bf_toc_4" title="Examples of Successful One-Word Titles">Examples of Successful One-Word Titles</a></li>
</ol>
</nav>
</div>
<h3 id="bf_toc_1">The Allure of Simplicity</h3>
<p><img alt='gamehall-org-1x-1-1055327' alt="Do you think that one word game titles are effective What are some examples of good one word game titles" src='https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/gamehall.org-1x-1-1055327.jpg'/></p>
<p>One-word game titles possess a certain elegance in their simplicity. They manage to distill the game&#8217;s concept, theme, or atmosphere into just a single word. This minimalist approach can be incredibly powerful, as it piques players&#8217; curiosity while leaving room for interpretation. Games like &#8220;Limbo,&#8221; &#8220;Journey,&#8221; and &#8220;Celeste&#8221; demonstrate that a well-chosen word can evoke emotions and spark interest, drawing players into the experience without revealing too much.</p>
</p>
<p><h3 id="bf_toc_2">The Intrigue of Mystery</h3>
<p><img alt='gamehall-org-s-l1600-1314201' alt="Do you think that one word game titles are effective What are some examples of good one word game titles" src='https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/gamehall.org-s-l1600-1314201.jpg'/></p>
<p>Mystery is a key element in storytelling, and one-word game titles play right into this. Titles like &#8220;Control,&#8221; &#8220;Subnautica,&#8221; and &#8220;Hollow Knight&#8221; create an air of intrigue, leaving players wondering about the nature of the game. These titles act as a hook, inviting players to explore further to uncover the secrets and stories hidden within. The element of mystery in one-word titles often serves as an invitation for players to step into the unknown.</p>
</p>
<p><h3 id="bf_toc_3">Memorability and Impact</h3>
<p><img alt='gamehall-org-word-choice-gems-scaled-1036778' alt="Do you think that one word game titles are effective What are some examples of good one word game titles" src='https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/gamehall.org-word-choice-gems-scaled-1036778.jpg'/></p>
<p>Short and impactful titles have a better chance of being remembered by players. One-word game titles can achieve this memorability by creating a distinct identity for the game. When a title is easy to remember, players are more likely to recommend it to friends, search for it in online stores, and engage with discussions about it. Games like &#8220;Doom,&#8221; &#8220;Bastion,&#8221; and &#8220;Nier&#8221; are prime examples of titles that are not only memorable but also carry weight and significance.</p>
</p>
<p><h3 id="bf_toc_4">Examples of Successful One-Word Titles</h3>
<p><img decoding="async" alt="Do you think that one word game titles are effective What are some examples of good one word game titles" src="https://19thnews.org/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/title-ix-timeline-1280x720-1.jpg"/></p>
<p>Several games have successfully embraced the one-word title approach, leaving a lasting impact on players and the industry alike:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>&#8220;Portal&#8221;</strong>: This title perfectly encapsulates the game&#8217;s central mechanic of using portals to navigate through puzzles.</li>
<li><strong>&#8220;Oxenfree&#8221;</strong>: The intriguing title suggests an air of mystery and sets the tone for the supernatural narrative.</li>
<li><strong>&#8220;Transistor&#8221;</strong>: The title hints at the central object in the game while also conveying a sense of transformation.</li>
<li><strong>&#8220;Braid&#8221;</strong>: A simple yet evocative title that matches the game&#8217;s unique time-manipulation gameplay.</li>
</ul>
<p><p>In conclusion, the effectiveness of a one-word game title lies in its ability to encapsulate the game&#8217;s essence, evoke curiosity, and create a memorable impact. While not every game can be boiled down to a single word, the success of titles like &#8220;Portal&#8221; and &#8220;Oxenfree&#8221; showcases the potential power of simplicity and intrigue. So, do one-word game titles work? The answer seems to be a resounding yes, as long as the chosen word resonates with the game&#8217;s core and captures players&#8217; imagination.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/do-one-word-game-titles-work/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unraveling the Intricacies of Suspended MLB Games and Player Rosters</title>
		<link>https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/unraveling-the-intricacies-of-suspended-mlb-games-and-player-rosters/</link>
					<comments>https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/unraveling-the-intricacies-of-suspended-mlb-games-and-player-rosters/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charlotte Gonzalez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 08:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Invitation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/?p=809</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Picture the scene: a thrilling MLB game is in full swing, with players giving their all to secure a victory. Suddenly, a storm rolls in,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Picture the scene: a thrilling MLB game is in full swing, with players giving their all to secure a victory. Suddenly, a storm rolls in, and the game is suspended. But what happens if players have left the team or new ones have joined when the game resumes? It&#8217;s a scenario that raises intriguing questions about the dynamics of suspended games and the intricacies of player rosters. Let&#8217;s dive into this fascinating topic and unravel the mysteries behind it.</p>
<div class="bf_toc_container">
<div class="bf_toc_title">Table Of Contents</div>
<nav>
<ol>
<li><a href="#bf_toc_1" title="The Suspension Conundrum: A Twist in the Game">The Suspension Conundrum: A Twist in the Game</a></li>
<li><a href="#bf_toc_2" title="Player Roster Transformations: From Then to Now">Player Roster Transformations: From Then to Now</a></li>
<li><a href="#bf_toc_3" title="The Role of New Additions: Integrating Fresh Faces">The Role of New Additions: Integrating Fresh Faces</a></li>
<li><a href="#bf_toc_4" title="The Unpredictable Chessboard: Strategy and Adaptation">The Unpredictable Chessboard: Strategy and Adaptation</a></li>
</ol>
</nav>
</div>
<h3 id="bf_toc_1">The Suspension Conundrum: A Twist in the Game</h3>
<p><img alt='gamehall-org-01kepner-astros1-superjumbo-3437754' alt="When an MLB game is suspended, what happens if players arent on the team when the game resumes and new players are on the roster" src='https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/gamehall.org-01kepner-astros1-superjumbo-3437754.jpg'/></p>
<p>When a Major League Baseball (MLB) game is suspended due to weather, darkness, or unforeseen circumstances, it introduces a unique challenge for teams, players, and even the fans. A suspended game essentially means that the game is halted before reaching its conclusion and will be continued at a later time. This unexpected twist can have a ripple effect on player rosters and team dynamics.</p>
<h3 id="bf_toc_2">Player Roster Transformations: From Then to Now</h3>
<p><img alt='gamehall-org-rujqz4nc6tkqrw1qhyho-6063781' alt="When an MLB game is suspended, what happens if players arent on the team when the game resumes and new players are on the roster" src='https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/gamehall.org-rujqz4nc6tkqrw1qhyho-6063781.jpg'/></p>
<p>One of the most intriguing aspects of a suspended game is how it impacts player rosters. Consider this scenario: a player is traded or injured between the time the game is suspended and when it resumes. What happens then? MLB has rules in place to address such situations, ensuring fairness and consistency.</p>
<p>According to MLB rules, when a game is suspended, the rosters of both teams remain unchanged for the resumed game. This means that even if a player has been traded or sent down to the minors, they are still eligible to participate in the continuation of the suspended game. This rule prevents any team from gaining an advantage by making last-minute roster changes before the game resumes.</p>
<h3 id="bf_toc_3">The Role of New Additions: Integrating Fresh Faces</h3>
<p><img alt='gamehall-org-nba-bubble-072820-getty-ftr-171qre7cfhsui1b802zc3k2pks-9208540' alt="When an MLB game is suspended, what happens if players arent on the team when the game resumes and new players are on the roster" src='https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/gamehall.org-nba-bubble-072820-getty-ftr-171qre7cfhsui1b802zc3k2pks-9208540.jpg'/></p>
<p>But what if a team has acquired new players after the original game was suspended? MLB rules also address this scenario. If a team has added new players to their roster after the original game but before its continuation, those new players are not eligible to participate in the resumed game. This ensures that the integrity of the game remains intact, as both teams play under the same conditions as when the game was suspended.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s important to note that while new players cannot participate in the resumed game, they are still officially part of the team and can play in subsequent games. The MLB rules strike a balance between accommodating new additions and maintaining fairness in the context of a suspended game.</p>
<h3 id="bf_toc_4">The Unpredictable Chessboard: Strategy and Adaptation</h3>
<p><img alt='gamehall-org-aulhdxhe5ormslulv7dd-1510801' alt="When an MLB game is suspended, what happens if players arent on the team when the game resumes and new players are on the roster" src='https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/gamehall.org-aulhdxhe5ormslulv7dd-1510801.jpg'/></p>
<p>The dynamics of suspended games and player rosters create an unpredictable chessboard for managers and teams. They must strategize not only for the immediate continuation of the game but also for the potential changes in circumstances that might arise due to player transactions or injuries.</p>
<p>For managers, it&#8217;s a delicate balance between utilizing the available roster to secure a victory in the resumed game while also considering the long-term implications for upcoming matches. The ever-changing landscape of player rosters adds an extra layer of complexity to the strategic decisions made by teams.</p>
<p>In conclusion, the world of MLB and suspended games is a realm of intricate rules and thoughtful considerations. The interplay between player rosters, team dynamics, and the unexpected twists of a suspended game adds to the excitement and challenges that define America&#8217;s favorite pastime. Whether it&#8217;s a traded player stepping up to the plate or a team adapting to unforeseen changes, the suspended game brings a touch of unpredictability to the sport, reminding us that anything can happen on the diamond.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://gamehallorg.github.io/p/unraveling-the-intricacies-of-suspended-mlb-games-and-player-rosters/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
